http://www.prab.com/service-support/privacy-policy/

OUR COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY
PRAB respects your privacy. We are particularly sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet and therefore we provide this Privacy Policy so you know about our online information practices and understand how we treat the information we receive about you from the Internet.
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
In general, you can browse our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We are however able to determine your IP address. We use your IP address to help administer our website, to measure the use of our website and to improve the content of our website. Our website’s registration and contact forms require users to give us contact information (like their names, addresses and email addresses).
We use customer contact information from our forms to send the user requested information about our company and our services. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
We may use your personal information for particular purposes such as market research and other marketing purposes; or for providing you with the latest service and promotional information that might be useful to you. We will not give or sell this information to any other company for its use in marketing or solicitation. If you have provided us your personal information and do not wish to receive further information from PRAB, you can send us an email as noted below and tell us that you do not want to receive future communications.
OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION
www.prab.com may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. By using this website you are agreeing to the terms of the www.prab.com Privacy Policy.
We reserve the right to modify our privacy policy as business needs require. We will post such changes on our website.
CONTACTING THE WEBSITE
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:
Webmaster
PRAB
5944 East N Avenue
Kalamazoo, MI, 49048
COPYRIGHT NOTICE
In General
This website is provided to you by PRAB Access to and use of this website and the services available at this website are subject to the following terms and conditions as set forth in this notice. By accessing or using the website or downloading materials from the website, you agree to be legally bound by the terms and conditions set forth below without any modification. Please, review them carefully. If you do not agree to the terms, do not use this website.
Copyright and Trademarks
Copyright © 2010 PRAB
5944 East N Avenue Kalamazoo, MI, 49048
Reserved
PRAB hereby grants to any person the right to reproduce and distribute copies of this work subject to the following conditions:
The information found on this website is constantly being updated. Users are responsible for checking the site on a regular basis to keep up with these changes. The publication is to be used for informational purposes only and may not be sold or distributed for commercial gain.
The above copyright notice must appear on every copy of the publication or any portion thereof.
Except as noted above, no right or license is granted under any copyright, patent, or trademark of PRAB to any other party.
Information contained in this publication is furnished free of charge. Because conditions of use are outside our control, PRAB makes no warranties, express or implied, and assumes no liability in connection with any use of this information.
Electronic Information Submitted to this Website
Any communication or material other than your personal information submitted to this website by electronic mail is the exclusive property of PRAB and is considered to be non-confidential and non-proprietary. Such communication may include without limitation questions, comments, suggestions and ideas. PRAB shall be free to use them for any purpose whatsoever without restriction or compensation.
Disclaimer
THE INFORMATION IN THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTIBILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. PRAB SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY ERRORS, OMISSIONS OR TECHNICAL INACCURACIES IN THIS WEBSITE.
Request a Quote
Contact Us
PRAB WORLD HEADQUARTERS 5801 East N Avenue, Kalamazoo, Michigan 49048
Sales: (800) 968-7722 / (269) 665-1085
Parts & Service: (800) 493-3462
Email: sales@prab.com
European Headquarters ul. Niemodlinska 87, K45-864 Opole, Poland
All Content ©2020 PRAB. All Rights Reserved.
Related Products
